question_data = [
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "Super Mario Bros. was the first video game ever created.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
          "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.",

          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The Kerbol System (from Kerbal Space Program) includes a Saturn analogue.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
                                          "question": "In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In the Monster Hunter Series, G-Rank is the highest possible prestige a Hunter can recieve.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
        ]
